Guide to the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 77 records
1905-2003
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
5569
5569-001
International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers.$bLocal 77 (Seattle, Wash.)
14 cubic feet 14 boxes
Records of the Union
Minute books (1905-96), and contract files (1936-2003).
Forms part of the Labor Archives of Washington.
Open to all users.
Received December 11, 2007.
Electric industry workers$xLabor unions$zWashington (State)$xArchives; Electricians$xLabor unions$zWashington (State)$xArchives; Electric industry workers$xLabor unions$zOregon$xArchives; Electricians$xLabor unions$zOregon$xArchives; Electric industry workers$xLabor unions$zIdaho$xArchives; Electricians$xLabor unions$zIdaho$xArchives; Labor$zWashington (State)$xHistory$vSources; Labor unions$zWashington (State)$xHistory$vSources; Labor movement$zWashington (State)$xHistory$vSources; Labor$zOregon$xHistory$vSources; Labor unions$zOregon$xHistory$vSources; Labor movement$zOregon$xHistory$vSources; Labor$zIdaho$xHistory$vSources; Labor unions$zIdaho$xHistory$vSources; Labor movement$zIdaho$xHistory$vSources; Minutes (Records); Collective labor agreements; Contracts; Membership lists; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers.$bLocal 77 (Seattle, Wash.)$vArchives; Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions; Washington (State); Seattle
- MEETING MINUTES, 1897-1988; SERIES I (Box-folder 1/1-4/19, 6/1-9/33, 11/1-14/18)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 11, 1945-1951; Subseries A (Box-folder 11/6)
    - Minutes: Unit 11, 1945-1951 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 100, Seattle, 1897-1983; Subseries B (Box-folder 4/7-4/14, 4/19, 7/1-7/6, 8/1-8/4, 12/1-12/12)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 Executive Board, 1919-1928 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 Executive Board, 1928-1930 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 E.W.B.A., 1949-1951 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local B77 Executive Board, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 Executive Board Seattle, 1953 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local B77 Executive Board Seattle, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local B77/77-100 Seattle:, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 Executive Board Seattle, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 4/14)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 Executive Board Seattle, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 4/19)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 Seattle, 1909-1911 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 Seattle, 1908 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 Seattle, 1907 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 Seattle, 1906 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 Seattle, 1905-1906 (Box-folder 7/5)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 Seattle, 1897-1900 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Minutes: Unit 100 (A) Seattle, Part 1, 1952-1956 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Minutes: Unit 100 (A) Seattle, Part 2, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Minutes: Unit 100 (A) Seattle, Part 3, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 8/3)
    - Minutes: Unit 100 (BA) Seattle, 1954-1958 (Box-folder 8/4)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers 77 Seattle, 1911-1912 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers 77 Seattle, 1912 (Box-folder 12/2)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers 77 Seattle, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 12/3)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers 77 Seattle, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Minutes: Unit 100 Seattle, 1955-1965 (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers B77 Seattle, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Minutes: Unit 100 Seattle, 1952-1956 (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Minutes: Unit 100 A Seattle, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Minutes: Unit 100 A Seattle, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Minutes: Unit 100/ 100 A Seattle, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Minutes: Unit 100 Seattle, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 101, PBX Operators, 1941-1962; Subseries C (Box-folder 7/15-7/16, 8/5, 8/7, 12/8)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers 77/ 77 B/ 101 PBX Operators, 1947-1953 (Box-folder 7/15)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers PBX Operators, 1941-1946 (Box-folder 7/16)
    - Minutes: Unit 101 (BA) Seattle, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 8/5)
    - Minutes: Unit 101 (BA) Seattle (PBX Operators), 1952-1957 (Box-folder 8/7)
    - Minutes: Unit 101 Seattle, 1953-1962 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Subseries D: IBEW 77, Unit 102, Seattle, 1948-1963 (Box-folder 8/6, 8/8)
    - Minutes: Unit 102 (A) Seattle, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 8/6)
    - Minutes: Unit 102 (A) Seattle (Operators), 1948-1963 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 103, Everett, 1951-1963; Subseries E (Box-folder 8/9-8/11)
    - Minutes: Unit 103 (BA) (W.C.T.) Everett, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 8/9)
    - Minutes: Unit 103 (BA) Everett, Part 1, 1952-1959 (Box-folder 8/10)
    - Minutes: Unit 103 (BA) Everett, Part 2, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 8/11)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 104, Chehalis, Centralia, 1935-1974; Subseries F (Box-folder 8/12-8/15, 14/8-14/12)
    - Minutes: Unit 104 (A + BA) Chehalis, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 8/12)
    - Minutes: Unit 104 (A + BA) Chehalis, 1952-1957 (Box-folder 8/13)
    - Minutes: Unit 104 (A + BA) Chehalis, 1958-1963 (Box-folder 8/14)
    - Minutes: Unit 104 Chehalis, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 8/15)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77-4/ B77 104 Chehalis, WA, 1948-1953 (Box-folder 14/8)
    - Minutes: Unit 104 A-BA Chehalis-Centralia, 1958-1966 (Box-folder 14/9)
    - Minutes: Unit 104 Chehalis-Centralia, 1953-1958 (Box-folder 14/10)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 745/ 77-4 Chehalis-Centralia, 1935-1940 (Box-folder 14/11)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77-4 Chehalis-Centralia-Morton, 1940-1948 (Box-folder 14/12)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 105, Aberdeen, 1951-1974; Subseries G (Box-folder 8/16-8/19, 14/1)
    - Minutes: Unit 105 (A + BA) Aberdeen, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 8/16)
    - Minutes: Unit 105 (A + BA) Aberdeen, 1953-1957 (Box-folder 8/17)
    - Minutes: Unit 105 (A + BA) Aberdeen, 1958-1963 (Box-folder 8/18)
    - Minutes: Unit 105 (A) Aberdeen, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 8/19)
    - Minutes: Unit 105A/ 105 Abeerdeen, WA, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 106, Longview, 1951-1974; Subseries H (Box-folder 2/1-2/6)
    - Minutes: Unit 106 (A + BA) Longview, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Minutes: Unit 106 (A + BA) Longview, Part 1, 1952-1955 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Minutes: Unit 106 (A + BA) Longview, Part 2, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Minutes: Unit 106 (A + BA) Longview, Part 3, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Minutes: Unit 106 (A + BA) Longview, Part 4, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Minutes: Unit 106 (A + BA) Longview, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 107, Newhalem-Diablo, 1951-1974; Subseries I: (Box-folder 2/7-2/10)
    - Minutes: Unit 107 (A) Newhalem-Diablo, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Minutes: Unit 107 (A) Newhalem-Diablo, Part 1, 1953-1958 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Minutes: Unit 107 (A) Newhalem-Diablo, Part 2, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Minutes: Unit 107 (A) Newhalem-Diablo, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 108 Ellensburg, 1951-1963; Subseries J (Box-folder 2/11-2/12, 14/15)
    - Minutes: Unit 108 (A) Ellensburg, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Minutes: Unit 108 (A) Ellensburg, 1953-1963 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Minutes: Unit 108 Ellensburg, 1954-1960 (Box-folder 14/15)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 109, Coeur d'Alene, Raymond, Ilwaco, 1951-1978; Subseries K (Box-folder 2/13-2/18, 7/9-7/10)
    - Minutes: Unit 109 (A) Coeur d'Alene, Idaho, 1954-1963 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Minutes: Unit 109 (A) Coeur d'Alene, Idaho, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Minutes: Unit 110 (A) Raymond, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Minutes: Unit 110 (A) Raymond, Part 1, 1952-1958 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Minutes: Unit 110 (A) Raymond, Part 2, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Minutes: Unit 110 Ilwaco, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Minutes: Unit 110 Raymond -Ilwaco, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 7/9)
    - Minutes: Unit 110 Raymond Ilwaco, 1950-1958 (Box-folder 7/10)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 111, Pasco, Richland, 1949-1974; Subseries L (Box-folder 2/19-2/22, 7/17, 13/1)
    - Minutes: Unit 111 (A) Pasco, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2/19)
    - Minutes: Unit 111 (A) Richland, Part 1, 1949-1956 (Box-folder 2/20)
    - Minutes: Unit 111 (A) Richland, Part 2, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 2/21)
    - Minutes: Unit 111 (A) Richland, Part 3, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 2/22)
    - Minutes: Unit 111 Pasco, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 7/17)
    - Minutes: Unit 111 (A + BA) Pasco, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 112, Olympia, 1940-1974; Subseries M (Box-folder 14/15, 14/17-14/18, 7/18-7/19, 13/2-13/6)
    - Minutes: Unit 112-A Olympia, 1956-1962 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Minutes: Unit 112-A, 1951-1956 (Box-folder 4/17)
    - Minutes: Unit 112 Olympia, 1940-1951 (Box-folder 4/18)
    - Minutes: Unit 112 A Olympia, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 7/18)
    - Minutes: Unit 112 A Olympia, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 7/19)
    - Minutes: Unit 112 (A + BA) Olympia, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Minutes: Unit 112 (A + BA) Olympia, Part 1, 1952-1957 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Minutes: Unit 112 (A + BA) Olympia, Part 2, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Minutes: Unit 112 (A + BA) Olympia, Part 3, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Minutes: Unit 112 (A + BA) Olympia, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 13/6)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 113, Spokane, 1952-1963; Subseries N (Box-folder 13/7-13/8)
    - Minutes: Unit 113 (A) Spokane (Radio Techs), 1952-1952 (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Minutes: Unit 113 (A) Spokane (Radio Techs), 1952-1963 (Box-folder 13/8)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 114, Wenatchee, 1953-1974; Subseries O (Box-folder 13/9-13/10)
    - Minutes: Unit 114 (A + BA) Wenatchee, 1953-1963 (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Minutes: Unit 114 (A + BA) Wenatchee, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 13/10)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 115, Bellingham/Burlington, 1936-1983; Subseries P (Box-folder 13/11-13/16, 14/2-14/5)
    - Minutes: Unit 115 (A + BA) Bellingham, 1951-1953 (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Minutes: Unit 115 (A + BA) Bellingham, Part 1, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Minutes: Unit 115 (A + BA) Bellingham, Part 2, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 13/13)
    - Minutes: Unit 115 (A + BA) Bellingham, Part 3, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 13/14)
    - Minutes: Unit 115 (A + BA) Bellingham, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 13/16)
    - Minutes: Unit 115 Burlington/ Bellingham, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 14/2)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77B Bellingham Unit, 1937-1945 (Box-folder 14/3)
    - Minutes: Unit 115 Burlington, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 14/4)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77/ B77-15 Bellingham-Burlington, 1936-1942 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 116, Renton, 1948-1974; Subseries Q (Box-folder 7/7-7/8, 13/17-13/22)
    - Minutes: Unit 116 Renton, 1948-1953 (Box-folder 7/7)
    - Minutes: Unit 116 A Renton, 1953-1959 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - Minutes: Unit 116 (A) Renton, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 13/17)
    - Minutes: Unit 116 (A) Renton, Part 1, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 13/18)
    - Minutes: Unit 116 (A) Renton, Part 2, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 13/19)
    - Minutes: Unit 116 (A) Renton, Part 3, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 13/20)
    - Minutes: Unit 116 (A) Renton, Part 4, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 13/21)
    - Minutes: Unit 116 (A + BA) Renton, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 13/22)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 117, Skagit Valley/Mt. Vernon/Sedro Wooley, 1941-1974; Subseries R (Box-folder 12/16, 13/23-13/25)
    - Minutes: Skagit Valley Tel Co Unit/ B77-17 Mt. Vernon/Burlington, 1941-1949 (Box-folder 12/16)
    - Minutes: Unit 117 (A + BA) S.V.T. Co., 1951 (Box-folder 13/23)
    - Minutes: Unit 117 (A + BA) Mount Vernon, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 13/24)
    - Minutes: Unit 117 (A + BA) Sedro Wooly, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 13/25)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 118, Everett, 1938-1979; Subseries S (Box-folder 1/1-1/5, 4/1-4/6, 14/16-14/18)
    - Minutes: Unit 118 A + BA Everett (Snohomish P.U.D) Part 1, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Minutes: Unit 118 A + BA Everett (Snohomish P.U.D) Part 2, 1953-1956 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Minutes: Unit 118 A + BA Everett (Snohomish P.U.D) Part 3, 1957-1961 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Minutes: Unit 118 A + BA Everett (Snohomish P.U.D) Part 4, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Minutes: Unit 118 A + BA Everett (Snohomish P.U.D.), 1972-1974 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Minutes: Unit 118 A Everett, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 Everett, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Minutes: Unit 118-A/ 118 A+B Everett, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Minutes: Unit 118-A/ 118 A-AB Everett, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77-B Everett, 1938-1945 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77-B Everett, 1945-1950 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Minutes: Unit 118/ 118 A Everett, 1954-1960 (Box-folder 14/16)
    - Minutes: Unit 118 A Everett / 118 BA Snohomish Co P.U.D., 1956-1966 (Box-folder 14/17)
    - Minutes: Unit 118 A Everett, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 14/18)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 119, Bremerton, 1956-1988; Subseries T (Box-folder 1/6-1/10, 11/3, 14/6-14/7)
    - Minutes: Unit 119 A Bremerton, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Minutes: Unit 119 A + BA Bremerton Part 1, 1947-1955 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Minutes: Unit 119 A + BA Bremerton Part 2, 1957-1961 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Minutes: Unit 119 A + BA Bremerton Part 3, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Minutes: Unit 119 A Bremerton, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Minutes: Unit 119/119A/ 119A-BA Bremerton, 1956-1962 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Minutes: Unit 119-A-BA / 119 A Bremerton, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Minutes: Unit 119-A+B Bremerton, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 120 A + BA, Ephrata, 1951-1974; Subseries U (Box-folder 1/11-1/14)
    - Minutes: Unit 120 A + BA Ephrata, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Minutes: Unit 120 A Ephrata Part 1, 1952-1959 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Minutes: Unit 120 A Ephrata Part 2, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Minutes: Unit 120 A Ephrata, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 1/14)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 121, Radio Units, 1938-1963; Subseries V (Box-folder 1/15, 7/11-7/14)
    - Minutes: Unit 121A, Radio Technicians, 1956-1963 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Roll Book and Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local Radio Technicians, 1941-1947 (Box-folder 7/11)
    - Roll Book and Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local B 77-2 Radio Servicemen, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 7/12)
    - Minutes: Unit 121"A", Radio Broadcast Unit, 1947-1954 (Box-folder 7/13)
    - Minutes: Unit 121"A", Radio Broadcast Unit, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 7/14)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 122, Puyallup/Sumner, 1951-1974; Subseries W (Box-folder 1/16-1/20)
    - Minutes: Unit 122 A Puyallup, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - Minutes: Unit 122 A Puyallup/Sumner Part 1, 1951-1957 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Minutes: Unit 122 A Puyallup/Sumner Part 2, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Minutes: Unit 122 A Puyallup/Sumner Part 3, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Minutes: Unit 122 A Puyallup/Sumner, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 1/20)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 123, Spokane, 1951-1974; Subseries X (Box-folder 1/22-1/25)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Minutes Local 77 Unit 123A Spokane, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Minutes Local 77 Unit 123A Spokane Part I, 1953-1957 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Minutes Local 77 Unit 123A Spokane Part II, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 1/23)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Minutes Local 77 Unit 123A Spokane Part III, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 1/24)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Minutes Local 77 Unit 123 Spokane, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 1/25)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 124, Coulee Dam, 1951-1974; Subseries Y (Box-folder 9/1-9/4)
    - Minutes: Unit 124A, BA Coulee Dam, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Minutes: Unit 124 A, BA Coulee Dam, 1953-1963 Part 1 of 2 (Box-folder 9/2)
    - Minutes: Unit 124 A, BA Coulee Dam, 1953-1963 Part 1 of 2 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - Minutes: Unit 124 A, BA Coulee Dam, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 125, Pullman/Portland, 1951-1974; Subseries Z (Box-folder 9/5-9/8, 4/16)
    - Minutes: Unit 125 A Pullman, 1953-1963 Part 1 of 2 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - Minutes: Unit 125 A Pullman, 1953-1963 Part 2 of 2 (Box-folder 9/6)
    - Minutes: Unit 125 A Pullman, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - Minutes: Unit 125 A Pullman, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Minutes IBEW 77-125 Northwest Communication Council (NCC) Portland, 1953-1957 (Box-folder 4/16)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 126, Clarkston, 1951-1974; Subseries AA (Box-folder 9/9-9/12)
    - Minutes: Unit 126 A Clarkston, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Minutes: Unit 126 A Clarkston, 1953-1963 Part 1 of 2, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - Minutes: Unit 126 A Clarkston, 1953-1963 Part 1 of 2, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 9/11)
    - Minutes: Unit 126 A BA, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 127, Okanagan, 1951-1974; Subseries BB (Box-folder 9/13-9/18)
    - Minutes: Unit 127 A BA, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 9/13)
    - Minutes: Unit 127 A, BA, Okanagan, 1952-1963 Part 1 of 2 (Box-folder 9/16)
    - Minutes: Unit 127 A, BA, Okanagan, 1952-1963 Part 1 of 2 (Box-folder 9/17)
    - Minutes: Unit 127 A, BA, Okanagan, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 9/18)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 128, Shelton, 1947-1974; Subseries CC (Box-folder 9/14, 9/19-9/20, 12/14-12/15)
    - Minutes: Unit 128 A BA Shelton, Washington, February 1973 (Box-folder 9/14)
    - Minutes: Unit 128 A Shelton, 1956-1963 (Box-folder 9/19)
    - Minutes: Unit 128 A, BA Shelton, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 9/20)
    - Minutes: Unit 128 A Mason County P.U.D., 1947-1953 (Box-folder 12/14)
    - Minutes: Unit 128 A Shelton, 1953-1959 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 129, Coulee Dam, 1951-1963; Subseries DD (Box-folder 9/21-9/22)
    - Minutes: Unit 129 A, BA Coulee Dam, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 9/21)
    - Minutes: Unit 129 A, BA Coulee Dam, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 9/22)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 130, Coeur d'Alene, 1951-1963; Subseries EE (Box-folder 9/23-9/26)
    - Minutes: Unit 130, A, BA, Coeur D'Alene, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 9/23)
    - Minutes: Unit 130, BA, Coeur D'Alene, 1952-1963, Part 1 of 3 (Box-folder 9/24)
    - Minutes: Unit 130, BA, Coeur D'Alene, 1952-1963, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 9/25)
    - Minutes: Unit 130, BA, Coeur D'Alene, 1952-1963, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 9/26)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 131, Kellog-Wallace, 1956-1963; Subseries FF (Box-folder 9/27-9/29)
    - Minutes: Unit 131 BA, Kellog-Wallace, 1956-1963, Part 1 of 3 (Box-folder 9/27)
    - Minutes: Unit 131 BA, Kellog-Wallace, 1956-1963, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 9/28)
    - Minutes: Unit 131 BA, Kellog-Wallace, 1956-1963, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 9/29)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 132, Moscow-Pullman, 1951-1963; Subseries GG (Box-folder 9/30-9/33)
    - Minutes: Unit 132 A, BA, Moscow-Pullman, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 9/30)
    - Minutes: Unit 132 BA, Moscow, 1952-1963, Part 1 of 3 (Box-folder 9/31)
    - Minutes: Unit 132 BA, Moscow, 1952-1963, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 9/32)
    - Minutes: Unit 132 BA, Moscow, 1952-1963, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 133, Kennewick, 1951-1963; Subseries HH (Box-folder 3/1-3/3)
    - Minutes: Unit 133 Kennewick, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - Minutes: Unit 133 (BA) Kennewick, Part 1, 1953-1957 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Minutes: Unit 133 (BA) Kennewick, Part 2, 1958-1963 (Box-folder 3/3)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 134, Wenatchee, 1951-1963; Subseries II (Box-folder 3/4-3/5)
    - Minutes: Unit 134 (BA) Wenatchee, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Minutes: Unit 134 Wenatchee, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 3/5)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 135, Spokane, 1951-1963; Subseries JJ (Box-folder 3/6-3/7)
    - Minutes: Unit 135 (BA) Spokane, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Minutes: Unit 135 (BA) Spokane, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 3/7)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 136, Sandpoint, 1951-1974; Subseries KK (Box-folder 3/8-3/10, 9/15)
    - Minutes: Unit 136 Sandpoint, Idaho, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Minutes: Unit 136 (A + BA) Sandpoint, Idaho, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Minutes: Unit 136 Sandpoint, Idaho, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - Minutes Unit 136 A, BA Sandpoint, Idaho, December 1974 (Box-folder 9/15)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 137, Kirkland, 1950-1963; Subseries LL (Box-folder 3/11-3/13)
    - Minutes: Unit 137 (A + BA) Kirkland, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Minutes: Unit 137 (A) Kirkland, Part 1, 1950-1956 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - Minutes: Unit 137 (A) Kirkland, Part 2, 1957-1963 (Box-folder 3/13)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 138, Spokane, 1951-1952, 1963; Subseries MM (Box-folder 3/14-3/15)
    - Minutes: Unit 138 (A) Spokane, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Minutes: Unit 138 (A) Spokane, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 3/15)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 139, Richland, 1951-1974; Subseries NN (Box-folder 3/16-3/18)
    - Minutes: Unit 139 (A + BA) Richland, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Minutes: Unit 139 Richland, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Minutes: Unit 139 Richland, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 3/18)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 140, Montesano/Elma/Richland, 1951-1974; Subseries OO (Box-folder 3/19-3/21)
    - Minutes: Unit 140 (BA) Montesano, 1952 (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Minutes: Unit 140 (BA) Montesano + Elma, 1951-1960 (Box-folder 3/20)
    - Minutes: Unit 140 (A) Richland, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 3/21)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 141, Lynden, 1954-1963; Subseries PP (Box-folder 3/22)
    - Minutes: Unit 141 (A + BA) Lynden, 1954-1963 (Box-folder 3/22)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 142, Seattle Tele-Construction, 1952-1986; Subseries QQ (Box-folder 6/1-6/4, 11/4)
    - Minutes: Unit 142 A Seattle Construction Part I, 1952-1958 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Minutes: Unit 142 A Seattle Construction Part II, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - Minutes: Unit 142 A Seattle Construction Part III, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Minutes: Unit 142 A Seattle Tele-Construction, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - Minutes: Unit 142A, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 143, Spokane Construction, 1952-1954; Subseries RR (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Minutes: Unit 143 A Spokane Construction, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 6/5)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 144, Tacoma, 1953-1954; Subseries SS (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Minutes: Unit 144 A and BA Tacoma, WA, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 6/6)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 145, Mt. Vernon, 1955-1963; Subseries TT (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Minutes: Unit 145 BA Mt. Vernon, WA, 1955-1963 (Box-folder 6/7)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 146, Coupeville/Oak Harbor, 1953-1973; Subseries UU (Box-folder 6/8-6/10, 14/13-14/14)
    - Minutes: Unit 146 A Coupeville, WA Part I, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Minutes: Unit 146 A Coupeville, WA Part II, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 6/9)
    - Minutes: Unit 146 A Oak Harbor, WA, 1973 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - Minutes: Unit 146 A Coupeville- Oak Harbor, 1962-1976 (Box-folder 14/13)
    - Minutes: Unit 146 A Coupeville, 1953-1962 (Box-folder 14/14)